Guide to the Alexander Papers 1665-1883 (bulk, 1717-1786) MS 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series 2: William Alexander, 1744-circa 1786
  - [William Alexander]--Business Papers. Lists of Debts, 1763 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - William Alexander--Business Papers. Shipping Tickets and Bills of Lading, 1749-1764 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - William Alexander--Business Papers. Division of Lands at Basking Ridge, 1764 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - William Alexander--Report of the Committee for Managing the Newark Dispute, 1771 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - William Alexander--Servant Indentures, 1764-1774 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - William Alexander--Business Papers. Snow "Unicorn", 1755-1759 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - William Alexander--Memoranda, 1751-1767, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - William Alexander--Estate Accounts, circa 1786 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Series 3: Mary Alexander, 1726-1766
  Series 3 consists primarily of correspondence and papers relating to the land holdings, merchant business, and estate of Mary Alexander. Much of her business was conducted with the merchant house of David Barclay & Sons of London. Invoices from this firm sometimes include samples of fabrics that Mary Alexander had requested or purchased. Most of the letters in the collection received by Mary Alexander are from this firm. Letters received by Mary Alexander are arranged chronologically. There are only two letters in the collection for which Mary Alexander is the sender. One is to Jonathan Scott (August 10, [1756]), the subject of which is unclear, and the other is to James Stevenson (September 17, 1757) and concerns business.
  Other business papers of Mary Alexander consist of accounts, bills, receipts, and invoices. One folder of material consists of legal and business papers regarding Mary Alexander's estate.
  - Mary Alexander--Letters Sent, 1756, 1757 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mary Alexander--Letter/Fabric Samples Sent to David Barclay & Son, 1749 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mary Alexander--Letters Received, 1736-1760 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples. Striped Satins, Silver Lace, Camlets, Grazette, etc., 1726 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples, 1730 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples. Grazette, 1735 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples. Silks, Grazette, Shagreen, Silikins, Lustring, 1737 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples, 1739 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples. Tabby, Camlet, 1741 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mary Alexander--Fabric Samples. Tabby, Grogham, 1760 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mary Alexander--Business Papers. Accounts, Bills, Invoices, 1737-1759, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mary Alexander--Business Papers. Letters, Bills of Exchange, Receipts, 1741-1759 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mary Alexander--Business Papers. Letter/account book, 1756-1766 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Mary Alexander--Business and Legal Papers, [1763] (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series 4: Other Correspondents, 1697-1815
  Series 4 consists of correspondence of persons other than James, William and Mary Alexander. This includes those members of the Alexander Family who are not extensively represented in the collection, and members of the Rutherfurd Family, which was related to the Alexanders by marriage. Also included in this series are several letters of John Prevoost, Mary Alexander's son by her first marriage. Letters written by members of the Rutherfurd Family, and by John Prevoost, are foldered separately, and arranged chronologically. All other letters are arranged in a single chronology. Frequently appearing in the series are letters to and from Joseph Murray, Cortlandt Skinner, and Thomas Bartow.
  - Other Correspondents--John Rutherfurd. Letters Sent, 1813-1814 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Other Correspondents--John Rutherfurd. Letters Received, 1784-1788, 1809, 1813 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Other Correspondents--Walter Rutherfurd. Letters Sent, 1792-1794, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Other Correspondents--Walter Rutherfurd. Letters Received, 1768, 1775, 1792-1796 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Other Correspondents--William Alexander Duer to John W. Francis, 1813 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Other Correspondents, 1697-1762, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Other Correspondents, 1763-1772 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Other Correspondents, 1773-1815 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Series 5: Legal Papers, 1665-1817
  Series 5 contains Legal Papers. For purposes of this arrangement, Legal Papers refers to those papers such as wills, contracts, conveyances, deeds, etc. that do not pertain to court cases. Because most of the legal papers in the collection have to do with the sale or transfer of lands in New Jersey, legal papers are arranged by county. The papers are then arranged chronologically within the county. Usually the parties to the land transfers are members of the Board of Proprietors transferring property among themselves, or to and from other holders of large tracts. In some instances, however, the parties are settlers (or proprietors), and Indians. Occasionally appearing among the legal papers are leases from landlords to tenants.
  In addition to the legal papers in boxes 12 -19, there are seven oversize deeds in the collection. These oversize items are not foldered, and are in boxes 59 and 60.
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County, 1685-1769 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County, 1770-1816 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Burlington County, 1700-1770 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, 1712-1749, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, 1750-1759 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, 1760-1765 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, 1766-1791 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Essex County, [1697]-1759, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Essex County, 1760-1817 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Gloucester County, 1768, 1770 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Hunterdon County, 1723-1769 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Middlesex County, 1672-1722 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Middlesex County, 1723-1744 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Middlesex County, 1745-1762 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Middlesex County, 1763-1775, 1792 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Legal Papers--Monmouth County, 1682-1745, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Monmouth County, 1746-1761 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Monmouth County, 1762-1775 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Morris County, 1739-1774, 1801, [1809] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Salem County, 1717 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Somerset County, 1695, 1716-1742, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Legal Papers--Somerset County, 1743-1753 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Legal Papers--Somerset County, 1754-1773 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Legal Papers--Sussex County, 1753-1815 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1665, 1701, 1705-1739 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1740-1744 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1745-1750 February (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1750 March-1759 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1760-1768 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Eastern Division, 1769-1774, 1783-1784 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Western Division, 1691, 1710-1744 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Western Division, 1745-1759 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--New Jersey. Abstracts of Deeds, 1741-1768 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Doobie & Drummond Estates--Folder 1, 1698-1747, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Legal Papers--Doobie & Drummond Estates--Folder 2, [1698-1747] (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legal Papers--Colony/State of New York, 1668-1733 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Colony/State of New York, 1734-1785, 1794, 1797, 1803 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Canajoharie, Albany County, New York, 1730-1773 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Mohawk Lands, 1722-1723, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Mohawk Lands, 1724 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Mohawk Lands, 1725-1743 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Legal Papers--Oblong or Equivalent Lands, 1708-1730 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Legal Papers--Second Nine Partners Tract, 1704-1714, 1734-1745 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Legal Papers--Second Nine Partners Tract, 1746 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Legal Papers--Second Nine Partners Tract, 1747-1749 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Legal Papers--Second Nine Partners Tract, 1750-1754 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Legal Papers--Colonies other than New Jersey and New York, 1720, 1729, 1742, 1765 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Legal Papers--Great Britain and Ireland, 1687-1801, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Legal Papers--Unspecified Counties and Colonies, 1716-1737, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Legal Papers--Unspecified Counties and Colonies, 1738-1748 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Legal Papers--Unspecified Counties and Colonies, 1744-1768, 1774, 1795 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Series 6: Surveys, [1681]-1804
  For purposes of this arrangement, Surveys are any papers created specifically to detail the boundaries of privately held land. Of these, there are two kinds: first, items that include scale drawings of the area surveyed; second; items usually referred to as returns of surveys, which give a written description of the boundaries of a tract, but have no drawing.
  Surveys are arranged by county, then alphabetically by the surname of the owner of the surveyed tract. In most instances, officials of the Surveyor General's office identified surveys by noting the names of the tract's owners on the verso of the survey. In almost every instance, even in the absence of such a notation, the surveyor himself names the owner(s) of the surveyed tract in the body of the survey. In instances when two or more owners are identified for a given tract, the survey is placed in the alphabet according to the surname of the first identified owner. Researchers should be aware that in their returns, officials were not consistent in the way that they listed the owners of tracts. Two surveys done for the same group of owners, therefore, might be alphabetized in the series under different letters, depending upon which owner's name was listed first on the return.
  In the Surveys series, are folders titled "Unidentified or Multiple Owners". These folders contain two types of material. The first type is surveys of tracts whose owners cannot be identified. The second type is surveys of several (usually adjacent) tracts, wherein no single owner's tract is identified as the subject of the survey.
  The last subseries in the Surveys series is of warrants granted by the Proprietors for tracts of land. These documents authorized the Surveyor General to survey a tract of a prescribed size for the grantee. The warrants do not name or designate specific tracts, but in many instances were issued as a preliminary to the undertaking of a survey, and thus correspond to items in the Surveys series. Almost all of the material of this kind in the collection was created by the East New Jersey Proprietors, with only one folder deriving from West New Jersey.
  Approximate inclusive dates of material within each folder are indicated on the upper right hand corner of the folders in this series.
  - Surveys--Bergen County. A - B (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. C - L (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. M - Ogden, David (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. Ogden, Gabriel - Post (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. R (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. S - Z (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, A - O (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, P - Z (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Bergen County. Ramapo Tracts, Unidentified or Multiple Owners (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Burlington County (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Burlington County. Unidentified or Multiple Owners (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Surveys--Essex County. A - Blackman (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Board - Crane (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Cross - H (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Essex County. I - N (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Essex County. O - Penn (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Perth - Price (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Essex County. R - V (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Essex County. W - Z (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Unidentified or Multiple Owners (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Survey Maps of Elizabeth Town Point Farm (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Essex County. Watercolor Survey Maps, Unidentified Tract (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Gloucester County (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Hunterdon County (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. A - B (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. C - Hankins (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. Harrison - J (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. K - Leonard, Samuel (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. Leonard, Thomas - Reid (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. Rogers - Z (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. Unidentified or Multiple Owners (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Middlesex County. Maps (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. A (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. B - Brimley (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Brown - Byllynge (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. C (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. D (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. E - F (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. G - Holmes, James (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Holmes, John - Jones, David (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Karr - Kinnan, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Knott, David (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Knott, David (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Knott, Peter (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. L - Layton (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Leconte - Lyells (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. M - N (No "O") (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. P - Potter, Daniel (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Potter, Joseph - Reid (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Rhe - Schenck, Abram (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Schenck, Roeloff -- Sharp, Anthony (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Sharp, Isaac - Sutvan (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. T - V (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Wainwright - White (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Wikoff - Z (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Monmouth County. Unidentified or Multiple Owners (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Morris County. A - Alexander. William (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Allin, David - Budd, Sarah (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Burnet - Demouth (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Dickinson - Ford, Jacob (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Ford, Samuel - H (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Morris County. J - L (No "I") (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Morris County. M - N (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Morris County. O - Ogden, Abraham (1774) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Ogden, Abraham (1775) - Peck (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Penns - Rapalje (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Rawls - Sip (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Skinner - Z (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Morris County. Maps (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Salem County (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Salem County. Maps (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. A (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. B - Dawken (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. Delancey - F (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. G - N (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. O - Schenck, Hendrick (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. Schenck, John - Z (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Somerset County. Maps (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. A - Alexander, Mary, Devisees of (Sept.1761) (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Alexander, Mary, Devisees of (Oct.1761) - Ayers, Elisha (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. B (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. C - Delancey, Oliver (1767) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Delancey, Oliver (1769-1772) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Delancey, Oliver (Sept.1773) - F (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. G - Lindsley, Levi (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Logan - M (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. O - Ogden, Robert (1766) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Ogden, Robert (1767) - Parker, James (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Perth (1764-1773) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Perth (1774-1776) - Price (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. R - Rutherfurd, Walter (1767) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Rutherfurd, Walter (1768) - Sharp, Anthony, Heirs of (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Sharp, Isaac - Sonmans, Peter, Heirs of (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Sonmans, Peter, Heirs of - Stephenson, Thomas (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Stevens - Z (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Sussex County. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties--New Jersey. A - D (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties--New Jersey. E - N (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties--New Jersey. O - Z (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties--New Jersey. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties--New Jersey. Maps (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Colonies and Counties. Maps (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Albany County, New York. Mohawk Lands, 1723, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--Canajoharie, Albany County, New York (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--Oblong or Equivalent Lands. Map, 1744, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--Second Nine Partners Tract. Maps and Field Work, 1743, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties & Colonies. Calculations, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--Unidentified Counties. Unidentified and Multiple Owners (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--Field Book of George Lesley. Somerset County, 1742 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Surveys--Field Book of James Lyne. [New Jersey], 1749 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Surveys--Field Book of Unidentified Surveyor. New Jersey, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. A (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. B - D (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. E - H (No "I") (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. J - L (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. M - R (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Surveys--East New Jersey--Warrants. S - Z (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Surveys--West New Jersey--Warrants (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Series 7: Court Papers, 1684-1818
  Court Papers are any papers, not including correspondence, which pertain to court cases. These include writs, warrants, motions, statements of case, pleas, and indictments. Also included in this series are the findings of Coroner's Juries. In most instances, the material is arranged by the name of the county in which a given trial took place, or in instances where the county is not specified or is unclear, by the name of the colony/state in which the trial took place. Courts whose jurisdictions were not confined to a single county appear in separate subseries.
  Criminal cases and civil cases are separate folder groups within each county, colony/state, or court subseries. Civil cases are arranged alphabetically by the surname of the plaintiff, criminal cases are arranged alphabetically by the surname of the defendant. In instances where more than one plaintiff or defendant is identified, the material is alphabetized by the surname of the first named plaintiff or defendant. In some instances, the spelling of surnames varies from one item to the next (e.g. Reyerse/Ryerse or Ten Eyck/Ten Eick/Ten Ike). In those instances, if the elements (date, venue, other proper names, etc.) of two or more documents indicate that they pertain to the same prosecution or suit, the items were filed together, regardless of the nonidentical spellings.
  In those instances when a court's jurisdiction is not restricted to a particular county, the material is arranged by the name of the court. Within the Court papers series, there are subseries for the New Jersey Court of Chancery, the New Jersey Court of Vice-Admiralty, and the New York Court of Admiralty.
  Cases heard by the New Jersey Supreme Court are sometimes identified as pertaining to specific counties within the colony/state. These Supreme Court cases are therefore interfiled within the county subseries. Other New Jersey Supreme Court cases are identified as having been heard in one or the other of the colony/state's capital cities (Perth Amboy, Burlington, or Trenton). Cases heard in any of these cities are filed together in a separate subseries (New Jersey Supreme Court). Civil and criminal cases are separate folder groups within this subseries.
  Cases heard by the New York Supreme Court are almost invariably identified as having been heard in New York City. New York Supreme Court cases are interfiled with other New York County civil or criminal cases. New York Supreme Court cases heard in Albany are interfiled with Albany County cases.
  Finally in the Court Papers Series is a subseries called Unidentified Cases. The first folder in this series consists of items that pertain to identifiable cases, but for which a location and court are unclear. Such cases are filed in a single alphabet of civil and criminal cases, by the name of the plaintiff. In criminal cases, the plaintiff is The King or The State.
  The remaining folders in the Unidentified Cases subseries consist of items that document procedures, testimony, arguments made, and authorities cited in cases that cannot be identified by plaintiff, defendant or venue. This material is sorted by form, and by date. Since it is not always possible to identify which material relates to civil and which to criminal cases, the material is interfiled in a single subseries. This material includes affidavits and depositions, opinions, arguments and briefs, and memoranda.
  Cases that can be identified by plaintiff and defendant have been recorded in a database.
  - Court Papers--Bergen County--Civil Cases (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Court Papers--Bergen County--Criminal Cases (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Court Papers--Bergen County--Coroner's Jury (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Court Papers--Bergen County--Court of Oyer & Terminer Minutes (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Court Papers--Burlington County--Civil Cases (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Court Papers--Burlington County--Criminal Cases (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Court Papers--Burlington County--Coroner's Juries (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Court Papers--Burlington County--Dockets (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Court Papers--Cape May County--Docket (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Court Papers--Essex County--Civil Cases. A - L (Box 40, Folder 10)